[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 3 + 7 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "10",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "10",
        "12",
        "11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 6 \u00d7 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "46",
      "options": [
        "48",
        "45",
        "46",
        "47"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 6 + 5 \u00d7 8?",
      "correctAnswer": "46",
      "options": [
        "47",
        "46",
        "45",
        "48"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 9 \u00d7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "37",
      "options": [
        "38",
        "37",
        "36",
        "39"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 8 \u00d7 7?",
      "correctAnswer": "61",
      "options": [
        "60",
        "63",
        "62",
        "61"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 6 + 9 \u00d7 9?",
      "correctAnswer": "87",
      "options": [
        "86",
        "87",
        "89",
        "88"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 6 + 8 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "46",
      "options": [
        "48",
        "46",
        "47",
        "45"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 9 + 2 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "19",
      "options": [
        "18",
        "20",
        "19",
        "21"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 10 \u00d7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "25",
      "options": [
        "26",
        "24",
        "25",
        "27"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 8 + 3 \u00d7 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "26",
      "options": [
        "27",
        "25",
        "26",
        "28"
      ]
    }
]